let us now revisit the solution concept
现在让我们重新审视解决方案概念
for extensive form games and let's start
进行广泛的形式游戏，让我们开始吧
by doing it let's start by looking at
通过这样做，让我们开始看
the following example in this game there
下面这个游戏中的例子
are a number of Nash equilibria and here
有一些纳什均衡，这里
is one of them BH see what is BH play
是其中之一BH看到BH玩什么
one goes down here and down here
一个人在这里和这里下来
whereas player two goes down here and
而第二个玩家在这里下来
down here under this strategy profile of
在此的战略概况下
course the outcome of the game is this
当然，游戏的结果是这样
one and the payoff to both players is
一个，两个玩家的收益是
five
五
let's first convince ourselves that this
首先让我们说服自己
is indeed a Nash equilibrium so let's
确实是纳什均衡，所以让我们
hold players one strategy fixed and see
固定玩家一项策略，看看
if player two can profitably deviate
如果玩家二可以有利地偏离
from their current response well what
从他们目前的反应来看
can they do they can say here I will
他们可以做到吗，我可以在这里说
instead of going C I would go D they
而不是去CI会去D他们
could say that but that would an impact
可以这么说，但这会产生影响
the outcome at all given that player two
给那个玩家两个，结果
is going down B and so that's not a
沿着B下降，所以这不是一个
profitable deviation wouldn't change
盈利偏差不会改变
their payoff the path to player two and
他们获得第二名玩家的收益，
the other thing they could do is say I'm
他们可以做的另一件事是说我
going to go down this this way but that
这样下去，但是那
would in fact worsen their payoff
实际上会恶化他们的收益
because they would end up here with a
因为他们最终会在这里
payoff of zero rather than the Pfizer
零回报而不是辉瑞
getting so player 2 cannot profitably
让玩家2无法获利
deviate from their current strategy what
偏离他们目前的策略是什么
apply what about player player one can
适用于玩家玩家可以做什么
they profitably deviate well what could
他们有利可图地偏离了什么
they do they could say okay rather than
他们会说可以，而不是说
go B I'll go a but then they will get a
去B我会去a但然后他们会得到a
payoff of three rather than the Pfizer
三分而不是辉瑞的回报
getting that not profitable and they
得到不赚钱，他们
could also say I'm going to go down G
还可以说我要去G
over here
在这里
but given that player 2 is going down e
但鉴于玩家2的失败率e
that wouldn't matter though in any case
无论如何都没关系
end up in this this outcome of the path
最终在这条路的这个结局中
of 5 and so that's not profitable
的5，所以没有利润
deviation either so neither player has a
要么偏差，要么没有球员有
profitable deviation then by definition
然后根据定义获利偏差
it's a Nash equilibrium but there's
这是纳什均衡，但有
something a little disturbing about this
对此有些困扰
equilibrium let's clear the slides it's
平衡让我们清除幻灯片
a little less messy and let's again
少一点混乱，让我们再次
write down the strategy for player 1
写下玩家1的策略
going be H and let's focus on Indy on
成为H，让我们专注于Indy
this node right there
这个节点就在那里
why would player 1 actually do H because
为什么玩家1实际上会做H，因为
G dominated the G they get a pair of 2
G统治了G他们得到了一对2
rather than 1 and so even though it did
而不是1，所以即使它确实
lead to a Nash equilibrium there's
导致纳什均衡
something a little troubling about it
有点困扰
and the way to understand it is by
而了解它的方法是
claiming that they would go down H here
声称他们会在这里H下
play 1 is threatening player 2 and
第一局威胁第二局玩家，
telling him listen do not consider going
告诉他听着不要考虑去
down here because I'm going to go down
在这里，因为我要下去
here therefore and you would get a zero
因此，在这里您将得到零
so you'd better go here and get a 5 is
所以你最好去这里得到5分
what player 1 saying is saying to player
玩家1对玩家说的是什么
2 but this is stretch is not credible
2，但是这是不可靠的
because after all player 2 said
因为毕竟玩家2说
player 1 says that but in fact it would
玩家1说，但实际上
not be in their interests I believe that
我相信不符合他们的利益
player 1 actually would go down here and
玩家1实际上会在这里下场
so how do we capture this in a formal
那么我们如何在正式形式中
definition that brings us to the notion
将我们带入概念的定义
of sub game perfect equilibria or sub
子游戏完美均衡或子
game perfection so let's first define
游戏完美，让我们先定义一下
the sub game it's a very obvious notion
子游戏是一个非常明显的概念
a looking at some node in the game node
看游戏节点中的某个节点
H the sub game of G rooted at H is a
H植根于H的G的子游戏是
restricted restriction of H to this to
H对此的限制
the descendants from from that from that
从那个的后代
node and similarly what are the set of
节点，类似的是什么
all sub games of G well look at all the
G的所有子游戏都很好看
nodes in G
G中的节点
the set of all sub games is simply all
所有子游戏的集合就是全部
the sub game routine at some node in G
G中某个节点的子游戏例程
and so a national Librium is a sub game
因此，国家图书馆是一个子游戏
perfect if it's restriction to every sub
如果对每个子项都有限制，则完美
game is also a Nash equilibrium for that
博弈也是那什纳什均衡
that sub game so if for example we go to
该子游戏，例如，如果我们去
the previous slide and we consider again
上一张幻灯片，我们再次考虑
clearing the slide for a second and if
清除幻灯片一秒钟，如果
we look at the national erbium b h c e
我们看一下国家b
and we decide to Nash equilibrium but
然后我们决定达到纳什均衡
among the sub games of this game the
在这个游戏的子游戏中
subtrees of this tree of this tree is
这棵树的这棵树的子树是
this sub tree so here's a sub game it's
这个子树，所以这是一个子游戏
a game of a single player player 1 and
单人游戏1和
the restriction of this Nash equilibrium
纳什均衡的限制
is simply that's action of going H but
简直就是走H的动作，
this is not an equilibrium in this very
这不是一个平衡
simple tree because there's a profitable
简单的树，因为有一个有利可图的
deviation to G for the player and so
玩家的G偏差等等
while the to Nashville above the whole
而到纳什维尔最重要的是
tree is restriction to the sub tree here
树是对子树的限制
is not a Nash equilibrium
不是纳什均衡
and therefore this Nash equilibrium is
因此，纳什均衡是
not a sub game perfect and so so we see
不是完美的子游戏，所以我们看到了
that in fact that captures the intuition
实际上捕捉到了直觉
of non-credible threat and notice also
不可信任的威胁，并且还应注意
that one special case of the sub tree is
子树的一种特殊情况是
the entire tree so sub game perfect
整棵树，所以子游戏完美
equilibrium has got to also be a
平衡也必须是
national ribbon so let's test our
国家功能区，所以让我们测试一下
understanding of this concept a little
对这个概念有一点了解
bit let's look at this tree and ask
让我们看看这棵树，问一下
ourselves what are some of the sub game
我们自己是什么子游戏
perfect equilibria there for example how
那里有完美的平衡
about a g CF well the claim is this in
关于ag CF的说法是
fact is sub being perfect now why is
现在事实是完美的，为什么是
that what is a
那是什么
G C and F so that gives you this outcome
GC和F，以便为您提供这种结果
over here and you can check there's no
在这里，你可以检查没有
profitable deviation but you can also
有利可图的偏差，但您也可以
ask in all the sub games is there
在所有子游戏中询问
profitable deviation well let's look at
有利可图的偏差让我们来看一下
some of the sub games well for example
例如一些子游戏
here there is a the stevie ation over
这里有一个方向
here but that would not be profitable
在这里，但那不会有利可图
for pair two because they would go down
对于第二对，因为他们会下去
from eight to three now but over here is
现在是八点到三点
their profitable deviation for example
例如他们的利润偏差
two player two not really because if
两个玩家两个不是真的，因为
they deviate it over here they would end
他们在这里偏离它会结束
up with a five random the ten they're
用五个随机数十个
getting how about over here is their
他们在这里过得如何
profitable deviation and this note to
有利可图的偏差和此注释
the agent one well no because if they
该代理人很好，因为他们
deviate they would get one rather than
偏离他们会得到一个而不是
two so in all sub games the restriction
在所有子游戏中有两个限制
of the strategy profile to that sub game
该子游戏的策略配置文件
is still a Nash equilibrium and a GCF is
仍然是纳什均衡，GCF是
in fact a sub game perfect Nash
实际上是一个完美的纳什子游戏
equilibrium how about bhce well the
平衡怎么样？
claim is that it's not well let's first
声称这不是很好，让我们先
write down the strategy bh b h and c e
写下策略bh bh和ce
and this is not sub game perfect for the
这不是子游戏的完美选择
reasons we saw before we saw that in
我们看到之前的原因
this sub game right here there is a
这个子游戏在这里有一个
profitable deviation for player one
玩家一的盈利偏差
namely to deviate over here and get to
即偏离这里并到达
rather than one and so it's not that
而不是一个，所以不是那个
being perfect and in fact for the same
是完美的，实际上是一样的
reason a HCF will not be sub game
HCF不会成为子游戏的原因
perfect let's write down what a h CF is
完美，让我们写下什么是CF
a h CF you can check that it's a Nash
啊CF你可以检查一下那是纳什
equilibrium but it is a nut sub game
平衡，但这是一个疯狂的子博弈
perfect again this sub game here is
再次完美，这里的子游戏是
allows for profitable deviation on the
允许在
part of the player one so even though
即使是玩家的一部分
it's what's called off path even though
这就是所谓的偏路
player 1 makes sure that him that he
玩家1确保他
never gets to visit this node by going
永远不会去访问这个节点
down here even so it's not like perfect
即使在这里也不是很完美
because had he gotten here he would not
因为他到了这里他不会
have done what he claims he would have
已经完成了他声称的目标
done and that gives us a good sense for
完成，这使我们对
what is sub game perfect Nash
什么是子游戏完美纳什
equilibrium is
平衡是